John, you're a toy. You and me
JOHN, 你只是个玩偶 你和我
- no future.
- 没有未来
Once some things are said...
(话一旦说出去...)
Remember what it was like to work a 60-hour week?
还记得一周工作60小时的日子吗?
You can't take them back.
(就收不回来了)
You are never going to get somebody who cares
你再也找不到任何一个
as much about finding Deirdre as I do.
比我更希望找到DIERDRE的人了
You shot yourself?
你射伤了自己?
Pretty lame, huh?
很没有说服力吧?
The damage is already done. Mom!
-后果已经发生了 妈妈!
You're not taking her away from me.
你别想把她从我身边夺走
Get out.
出去
I needed you to see something.
我想让你看些东西
They said they stole it from Mike's garage.
他们说是从MIKE的车库里找到的
Is that blood?
那是血吗?
Bree van de Kamp believed
(BREE VAN DE KAMP信奉)
in old-fashioned values.
(老式的价值观)
Things like respect for god...
(比如对上帝的尊敬...)
the importance of family...
(对家庭的重视...)
and love of country.
(和对祖国的热爱)
In fact, Bree believed so strongly in her values,
(事实上, BREE太过执著于自己的价值观)
It was always a shock whenever she was confronted
以至于每当她面对与她价值观相异的人
With those who didn't.
她总是会感到震惊
It's not mine.
这不是我的
You promised the cheating had stopped, Rex.
你保证不再背叛我了, REX
You promised.
你保证了
Could we not yell at each other?
我们可以不要冲着对方嚷嚷吗?
I'm feeling really lousy today.
我今天感觉很不好
I want you out of the house!
我要你离开这幢房子!
Bree, look at me.
BREE, 看着我
It's not mine.
这不是我的
Well, then, whose is it?
好吧, 那么, 这是谁的?
It just didn't magically appear in my laundry basket.
它不可能像变魔术一样突然出现在 我的洗衣篮里吧
Well, I'm not the only guy in this house
似乎, 在这个家里我不是唯一一个
That uses that hamper.
用这东西的人
No.
不
Sorry.
抱歉
Andrew is still a child.
ANDREW还是个孩子
He's 16. it's not unheard of.
他16岁了, 这不是什么稀罕事
Honey, you have to talk to him.
亲爱的, 你必须和他谈谈
And tell him what?
跟他说什么呢?
Tell him that we found his condom,
跟他说我们找到了他的避孕套
and that he is forbidden from, you know...
告诉他禁止那个...
I can absolutely tell him that we think he's too young,
我完全可以告诉他我们觉得他还太小
but I don't think it's going to do any good.
但我不认为这会有什么效果
Well, then, the least we can do is go search his room,
那么, 我们至少可以搜搜他的房间
And if we find any more of these, we'll confiscate them.
如果发现还有这东西, 就全部没收
And that will accomplish what?
那样的话又能怎样呢?
Well, if we take away his condoms, maybe
如果我们拿走他的避孕套, 也许
He's a teenage boy. We could take away his penis,
他是个十几岁的男孩了 我们就算把他的“小兄弟”拿走
He'd still try to have sex.
他仍然会试着去做爱
Well, we can't put it back in his room.
但我们不能把这个放回他的房间
I mean, that would be
我的意思是, 那好像是
Like we're condoning him having premarital sex.
我们在默许他发生未成熟的性关系
Bree, let me put this another way.
BREE, 让我换个角度来说吧
Do you want to become a grandmother?
你想成为奶奶吗?
Yes, Bree believed in old-fashioned values.
(是的, BREE信奉老式的价值观)
But she also believed...
(但她同样相信...)
it was better to be safe
(与其事后后悔)
than sorry.
(不如事前安全)
Each new morning in suburbia brings with it
(在郊区, 每一天早晨的到来)
a new set of lies.
(都伴随着一系列的谎言)
Little white lies, told not to hurt...
(小小的无恶意的谎言 目的不是伤害他人...)
Morning, Mrs. Petchel. you look lovely today.
早上好, PETCHEL夫人 你看上去真漂亮
But to make life more pleasant,
(而是使生活更加美好)
they tell these lies to protect themselves
(他们说这些谎话来保护自己)
and their reputations.
(和他们的声誉)
Oh, for god's sake. this is unbelievable.
哦, 上帝啊, 这真是难以相信
That's the last time I do my banking online.
那是我最后一次使用网上银行业务
Of course, every now and then, the day arrives
当然, 时不时地, 终有一天
When someone finally decides to tell the truth.
会有人决定说出真相
He was shot?
他被射伤了?
How could you not tell us about this?
你怎么可以不告诉我们这事?
He was embarrassed. he said it was an accident.
他觉得很尴尬, 还说那是一次意外
Oh, don't look at me like that. accidents happen.
哦, 别这样看着我, 有时候的确有意外
We know that you want to trust Mike,
我们知道你希望信任MIKE
but he had a dead woman's jewelry in his garage.
但我们在他车库里发现了 一个死去的女人的珠宝
Now, did he? we don't know that for sure.
是吗? 我们还不能确定
All we know
我们所知的是
is that Lynette's kids turned up with it.
LYNETTE的孩子发现了那个
So what are you saying, that the twins murdered Martha?
那么你的意思是那对双胞胎杀了MARTHA?
Well, I wouldn't put it past them.
我可不这么认为
I'm saying that that is about as likely
我是说
as Mike having done it.
MIKE也不可能是凶手
He's a good guy. I know him.
他是个好人, 我了解他
I mean, he's
我的意思是, 他是
- he's Mike.
- 他是MIKE
Honestly, I don't think Mike did it, either,
老实说, 我也觉得不是MIKE干的
But if we don't call,
但是如果我们不报告的话
we're guilty of withholding evidence.
我们有扣留证据的嫌疑
Well, you know what? if he is innocent,
知道我怎么想吗? 如果他是清白的
this should be a simple matter to clear up.
那么事情很快就能澄清
But we will do whatever you want us to do.
但我们会做任何你想让我们做的事
Okay, call.
好的, 打电话吧
So shall I just dial 911?
那么我该直接打911吗?
Well, it's not really an emergency.
- 这也不能算是紧急情况
There was a murder.
而是一次谋杀
Well, not recently, and I prefer not to tie up the line.
而且不是最近发生的 我想还是不要占用别人的电话时间了
Will you just call?
你能不能快点打啊?
Hey.
嗨
My Mom will be home any minute.
我妈妈随时可能回来
She'll freak if she sees you here.
如果她看到你在这儿, 她会发疯的
Oh, I just wanted to deliver this personally.
哦, 我只是想亲自把这送过来
I'm having a party.
我在准备一个派对
You know she doesn't want us to see each other.
你知道她不希望我们再见面了
Well, you got to come.
你应该来
I
我
- you're the reason I'm doing this.
- 我这么做都是为了你
I'll try to talk to my Mom, okay?
我会试着和我妈妈谈的, 好吗?
But you really got to go.
但你真的应该走了
Hey, Mrs. Sol韘.
嗨, SOLIS夫人
I'm sorry. Do I know you?
不好意思, 我们认识吗?
Yeah, I'm Justin
我是JUSTIN
- John's roommate.
- JOHN的室友
Been waiting forever for you to show up.
我等了你好久了
Really? why?
真的? 为什么?
I want to do you a favor.
我想帮你一个忙
What kind of favor?
什么忙?
Well, John says that
JOHN说
you can't exactly afford a gardener right now,
你现在没钱请园丁了
And I told him I'd be happy to do it...
我告诉他我很愿意...
for free.
免费服务
You want to mow my lawn for free.
你想要免费为我修草坪?
Mow your lawn, water your flowers,
修草坪, 浇花
trim your bushes.
还有剪枝条
I could do everything John did for you.
我能做JOHN为你做的任何事
That's very generous of you, but I don't think so.
你很客气, 但我不想你来做
Why?
为什么?
Because my husband is home quite a lot these days.
因为这段日子我丈夫经常在家
If any bush needs trimming, he takes care of it.
如果需要剪枝条了, 他能去做
Well, this is a very beautiful yard.
这是个美丽的院子
I'm sure it could use a little extra attention.
我敢肯定它需要一些额外的照料
I'm flattered, but no, thank you.
我很荣幸, 但是不用了, 谢谢
Mrs. Sol韘, please.
SOLIS夫人, 拜托了
Did I mention why my husband's home a lot?
我告诉过你为什么我丈夫经常在家吗?
He's under house arrest.
他正被软禁中
Oh?
噢?
He has a lot of anger toward the government right now,
他现在对政府很气愤
and he's just dying to find someone to take it out on.
正想找个人出出气呢
Hey, guys?
嗨, 伙计们?
This isn't a hockey rink. can you take it outside?
这儿可不是曲棍球场 你们能到外面去玩吗?
Hi, honey. how was your day?
嗨, 亲爱的. 你今天过得好吗?
I didn't get the V.P. gig.
我没能升为副主管
Oh, tom, I am so sorry.
哦, TOM, 我真为你感到难过
It just doesn't make any sense to me.
我真是难以理解
I mean, I'm Peterson's go-to guy,
我是PETERSON最好的手下
So how does Tim Duggan,
TIM DUGGAN
the biggest blowhard in the office,
这个办公室里最大的吹牛鬼
get promoted to vice president over me?
怎么能在我之前升上副主管呢?
I thought you liked Tim Duggan.
我以为你喜欢TIM DUGGAN
I do. I just...
我是喜欢他. 只是...
I don't know. I just
我不知道. 我只是
-
I really wanted that promotion.
我真的很希望能够晋升
Hey, boys, can you please take the Stanley cup finals outside?
嗨, 孩子们, 你们能不能 到外面去举行“STANLEY杯决赛”啊?
Well, did you tell Mr. Peterson that you wanted the job?
你告诉过PETERSON先生 你想要这份工作吗?
I have worked at that firm for 8 1/2 years.
我已经在那个事务所里工作了8年半了
Duggan's been there for less than two.
DUGGAN来了还不到2年
I am not going to beg.
我不想去乞求别人
I'm not saying to beg.
我不是要你去乞求别人
You just have to step up from time to time.
有时候你必须主动站出来
You have to see your opportunity and take it.
必须看到你的机遇并抓住它
Nobody respects a shrinking violet.
没有人尊敬羞怯的人
There is more than one, you know, leadership style.
领导方式有很多种
Mine is quiet, but effective.
我的是安静, 但有效
Take that racket outside!
把那球拍拿到外面去!
Well, whatever works for you.
反正适合你的就好
Susan.
SUSAN
Hey, sexy. where you been?
嗨, 甜心. 你上哪儿去了?
I called you twice. you avoiding me?
我打了两次电话给你. 你在躲着我吗?
Don't be silly. why would I do that?
别傻了. 我为什么要那么做啊?
No, I've just been really busy grocery shopping.
不, 我只是忙于购买日用品
For two days? must be pretty well stocked.
两天都是? 肯定有不少库存吧
How about dinner tonight?
今晚一起吃晚饭好吗?
Uh...
呃...
Dinner tonight? um...
今晚一起吃晚饭? 呃...
You okay?
你没事吧?
Can you hold these a sec?
你能拿一下这些东西吗?
Up against the car!
背靠车站好!
You have the right to remain silent.
你有权保持沉默
Anything you do say can be used against you
你所说的任何事都可能被
in a court of law.
作为陈堂证供
You have the right to consult an attorney.
你有权请律师
If you cannot afford an attorney,
如果你无法负担律师费
one will be appointed to you.
将会有一名律师被指派给你
So get this
我听人说
-
Zach young's throwing a pool party Saturday night.
ZACH YOUNG将在周六开一个泳池派对
Sent out a bunch of formal invitations,
他送出了一大堆正式的邀请函
complete with fancy lettering.
上面都是漂亮的字体
I'm surprised he didn't spritz them with after-shave.
我真奇怪他怎么没向他们喷美容水
What is wrong with nice invitations?
精美的邀请有什么错啊?
Mom, it's a pool party.
妈妈, 那是一个泳池派对
Why couldn't he have just passed out flyers in the quad?
为什么他不能只是在邻里发发传单啊?
'Cause he's genetically incapable of being cool?
因为他天生就不懂得怎样才酷?
So, uh, are you going?
那么, 嗯, 你去吗?
Mm, maybe.
嗯, 也许吧
I mean, um, Lisa and Justin
我是说, LISA和JUSTIN
-
Some of the guys thought it'd be fun to swim.
一些家伙觉得能游泳会很有趣
We can always bail
我们随时可以开溜
if it's as lame as we think it's going to be.
如果那个派对 的确像我们想象的那么无趣的话
Oh, is, um, Lisa your friend with the pierced navel?
嗯, LISA是你的那个 在肚脐上穿洞的朋友吗?
Yeah.
是啊
You've been spending a lot of time together lately,
你们两个最近经常在一起
haven't you?
不是吗?
I guess.
我想是的
Oh, uh, Andrew,
哦, 嗯, ANDREW
I'm going to want you home by 11:00 on Saturday.
我希望你周六晚11点前回家
11:00?
11点?
Mom, it's not even a school night.
妈妈, 那连校园活动都算不上
Bree, a curfew isn't going to do any good.
BREE, 宵禁不会有什么效果的
You may be able to abdicate all your parental responsibility,
你也许能放弃所有作为家长的责任
But I cannot.
但我不能
What
这
- What's going on here?
- 到底是怎么回事?
Would this have to do with the condom you left in my room?
是不是和你留在我房间里的避孕套有关?
As a matter of fact, it does,
事实上, 是的
And just so we're clear, if you get Lisa pregnant,
我们把话说清楚吧, 如果你让LISA怀孕了
You will marry her.
你就要娶她
Andrew, this is not funny.
ANDREW, 这并不好笑
Mom, trust me
妈妈, 相信我
- this is very funny,
- 这非常好笑
mostly because the condom wasn't mine.
主要是因为那个避孕套不是我的
You suck, you know that?
你是个混球, 知道么
So obviously we need to talk.
很明显, 我们需要谈谈
I'm still a virgin, if that's what you want to know.
我依然还是一个处女 如果这就是你们想知道的
Well, good.
很好
But why on earth would you need a condom?
但你到底为什么需要一个避孕套啊?
Because I'm planning on having sex,
因为我在计划和别人做爱
and I don't want to get pregnant.
而我不希望怀孕
Danielle, you are president of the Abstinence Club.
DANIELLE, 你是禁欲俱乐部的主席啊
I wasn't planning on running for a second term.
我并没希望竞选连任
John.
JOHN
John Rowland? I thought you broke up with him.
JOHN ROWLAND? 我以为你和他分手了
No, he broke up with me,
不, 他甩了我
and you want to know why? Because I wouldn't do it.
你们知道为什么么? 因为我不肯做爱
Well, if that's the type of boy he is, then good riddance.
如果他是那样的男孩 正好趁此机会离开他
Mom, every boy at my school is that type of boy.
妈妈, 我学校里每个男孩都是那样的
Besides...
另外...
It's different with John.
JOHN的情况不同
I love him.
我爱他
Oh, sweetheart,
哦, 宝贝儿
just because you give a boy sex
并不是你和一个男孩做爱了
doesn't mean you'll get love in return.
就能换回他对你的爱
So maybe I'm being stupid.
也许我是很傻
What's the big deal? It's just sex.
那又怎样呢? 只不过是性
Honey, I am looking out for your happiness.
宝贝儿, 我是为了你的幸福着想
Now, I understand what it's like to be young
我明白年轻的感觉
and feel urges,
那种冲动
but I waited until I got married,
但我一直等到了婚后
as did your father, and it was so much better.
你爸爸也是一样, 那样比你现在好多了
But daddy ended up cheating on you.
但爸爸最后还是背叛了你
Yes, well...
是的, 嗯...
And ever since he moved back in,
自从他搬回来以后
you've been miserable.
你就一直很可怜
Why would you say that?
你为什么那么说?
The walls between our bedrooms are paper-thin.
我们卧室之间的墙像纸一样薄
I hear more stuff than I probably should.
我听到了很多也许不该听到的东西
Oh.
哦
Look, Mom, I love you a lot,
你看, 妈妈, 我很爱你
But you really are the last person
但你真的是最没有资格
to ever give anyone advice about sex and happiness.
在性和快乐上给别人建议的人
Have you seen these?
你见过这些吗?
Five more past due notices.
又是五个逾期未支付的通知
Don't worry. I'm handling it.
别担心, 我能处理
How? how are you handling this?
你怎样处理?
Can I please finish my sandwich?
能让我先吃完三明治吗?
Have you seen our checking account lately?
你有没有看过我们最近的支票账号?
We're broke.
我们破产了
And then we have the mortgage payment coming up,
而且很快我们就要付抵押款
we have property taxes
- 我们还有财产税
- Gabby, it's going to be okay.
GABBY, 没事的
No, it's not. We are seriously screwed,
不, 我们面临着严峻的问题
and I am freaking out that you're not freaking out.
你一点都不担心的态度快让我发疯了
Look, things will turn around.
你看, 情况会好转的
When?
- 什么时候?
I don't know when.
我不知道什么时候
But we're lucky people, and we'll be lucky again.
但我们是幸运的人, 我们会再次走运的
What is that?
那是什么?
It's the lawnmower.
是除草机
We got a new gardener today.
我们今天有了一个新的园丁
It's not going to cost us a cent.
而且是免费的
The kid's a friend of John's.
- 这孩子是JOHN的朋友
Carlos
CARLOS
-
And he said that he'd do the lawn for free.
而且他说他愿意免费打理草坪
Can you believe it?
你能相信吗?
We are lucky people.
我们很幸运
You got it!
你成功了!
Yeah, Duggan!
是啊, DUGGAN!
Go, man!
上啊, 伙计!
All right! Hey guys, good to see you again.
很好! 嗨, 伙计们 很高兴再次见到你们
Hi.
嗨
Don't look so glum. you're going to get a hit.
别阴沉着脸. 你马上要上场了
Oh, it's not that.
哦, 不是那样的
This is my "hating Tim Duggan" look.
这是我“讨厌TIM DUGGAN”的表情
Oh! Duggan connects.
哦! DUGGAN成功击打了
Look at the job-stealing bastard run.
看那个偷别人工作的混蛋跑得欢啊
Duggan is really showing some of that glory-hounding,
GGAN正施展出他著名的
ass-kissing hustle that he is so well-known for.
追逐虚荣的混账的匆匆小步
I forgot how much fun you are when you're bitter.
我都忘了你心怀怨恨的时候是多么有趣
Oh, look, he's stretching for extra bases,
哦, 看啊, 他冲向额外的垒包了
just like he stretched for extra territory
就好像冲向额外的业务领域
screwing over unsung utility player tom Scavo.
狠狠地打击了 未得到赏识的全能选手TOM SCAVO
Ooh! down goes Duggan! Duggan goes down!
哦! DUGGAN倒下了! DUGGAN倒下了!
That's gotta hurt.
那一定很疼吧
Well, the glory hound is tagged out,
追逐虚荣的家伙被触杀了
and, well, he's going to have to deal
看来, 他这次
With some tough dirt stains, that Tim Duggan.
出大洋相了, 那个TIM DUGGAN
Tom...
TOM...
Oh, no, look, I'm sure he's just grandstanding.
哦, 不, 你看 我肯定他只是在小题大作
Oh, my god.
哦, 天啊
Holy crap.
不是吧
It's only a pool party. everyone's going to be there.
只是一个泳池派对, 大家都会参加的
I said no.
我说了“不”
What are you going to do,
你想怎么样呢
Keep a boy-free zone around me until I'm 18?
在我周围建一个男孩免进区直到我18岁?
You can see boys in a couple years,
再过几年你就可以和男孩们约会了
Just not that boy.
就是不能和那个男孩
Why do you hate Zach?
你为什么讨厌ZACH?
I don't hate Zach.
我不讨厌ZACH
I just think he's sort of crazy.
我只是觉得他有点疯疯癫癫
Mom, I've heard people call you sort of crazy.
妈妈, 我听到过别人说你疯疯癫癫
Well, I'm adorable crazy, and he's rampage crazy.
我是疯得可爱, 而他是疯得狂暴
Susan Mayer?
SUSAN MAYER?
Yeah.
是的
I'm Detective Copeland.
我是COPELAND侦探
I'm investigating the murder of Martha Huber.
我负责侦察MARTHA HUBER谋杀案
I need to talk to you about Mike Delfino.
我想和你谈谈MIKE DELFINO的事
Do you remember seeing Mr. Delfino
你是否记得在上月7号
On the 7th of last month?
见过DELFINO先生?
Is the 7th important?
7号很重要吗?
Well, we believe it was the night
我们相信
that Martha Huber was murdered.
MARTHA HUBER是在那一晚被谋杀的
She was last seen
最近一次有人见到她
at the grocery store around 9:00,
是9点左右在杂货店
and then she didn't show up
然后她没有去
for a dentist appointment the next morning.
第二天在牙医诊所的预约
What day was that?
那是礼拜几?
It was a Sunday.
礼拜天
Oh, my god, yes.
哦, 天啊, 是的
Yes, yes.
是的, 是的
Yes, I-I was with Mike that night.
是的, 我-我那晚和MIKE在一起
You're sure.
- 你确定?
yes, I was.
是的
Yep, it was a big night for us relationship-wise.
是的, 那一晚对于我们关系意义重大
It was the first time that we...
那是我们第一次
The first time you...
你们第一次...
Did it.
做了
The first time they did it.
他们第一次做爱
Julie!
- JULIE!
Well, it was.
那的确是啊
How did you know?
- 你怎么知道的?
I'm not clueless.
我可不是毫无头绪
I found men's boxers in the clothes hamper.
我在衣篮里发现了男人的运动短裤
Oh, don't write that down.
哦, 别把那个写下来
Oh, but this is good. you can let Mike go.
哦, 不过这很好. 你们可以放过MIKE了
He's innocent.
他是无辜的
Well, assuming everything you're telling me is true.
如果你告诉我的都是真的话
It's true. The next morning,
是真的. 第二天早上
she made pancakes in the shape of little hearts.
她做了小小的爱心形状的薄烤饼
Seriously. Little hearts.
真的, 小小的爱心
Oh, god.
哦, 天啊
Justin, what are you doing up here?
JUSTIN, 你在这儿干什么啊?
Uh, I finished the hedges.
嗯, 我完成了树篱
Is there anything else Mr. Sol韘 wants done?
SOLIS先生还想要我做什么吗?
I don't know. he's not here.
我不知道, 他不在这儿
He had a meeting with his lawyer.
他和他的律师有个会要开
So I guess that means we're all alone.
那么我想我们是单独在一起了
No, that means I'm all alone.
不, 那意味着我是单独一人
You're leaving.
你要离开了
I'm not in a hurry.
我不急
Come on, maybe we could hang out for a little while.
来吧, 也许我们能一起待一小会儿
I don't think so.
我不这么想
Come on.
来吧
If you just got to know me, you'd see I can be lots of fun.
如果你了解我的话 你会发现我这人很有意思
All my friends say so.
我的朋友都这么说
Well, I'm not interested in becoming one of your friends.
我没有兴趣成为你的朋友之一
Get out of my bedroom.
从我的卧室离开
Come on, Mrs. Sol韘, be nice.
拜托, SOLIS夫人, 听话一点
You shouldn't have done that.
你不该那么做
Do you know how easy it would be
你知道我有多容易
for me to call my husband and tell him
打电话给我丈夫并告诉他
what you just tried to do?
你刚才试图想做的事情吗?
Not easy as it'll be
并不像
for me to tell him what happened between you and John.
我告诉你丈夫你和JOHN的事那样容易
I-I'm sorry, Mrs. Sol韘,
我-我很抱歉, SOLIS夫人
But you're going to have to be nice to me...
不过你要对我好一点...
at least once.
至少一次
Mike!
MIKE!
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
Uh, yeah, yeah. I'm a little bit embarrassed.
嗯, 是的, 是的, 我有点尴尬
I must be the talk of the neighborhood.
我肯定成了邻居们的话题
No. not really, no.
不, 真的不是, 不
So guess what
你猜怎样
-
I'm your alibi.
我为你提供了不在场证明
I told the police that we were...
我告诉警察我们...
Together the night that Mrs. Huber was killed
HUBER夫人被杀的那一晚我们在一起
and that I could never forget that night.
还有我永远忘不了那一晚
So you don't think I killed Mrs. Huber.
所以你不认为是我杀了HUBER夫人
No. no, of course not.
不, 不, 当然不
I could never think you killed anybody,
我从没想过你会杀任何人
even if I wasn't your alibi, which I am.
即使我不是你的不在场证人 而事实上我是
Okay, I'm, um...
我, 嗯...
I'm going to go take a shower.
我要去冲一把澡
Jail's kind of gross.
监狱里很脏
I'll call you later, okay?
我晚点打电话给你, 好吗?
Sure. when?
好的. 什么时候?
Later.
晚一点
All right, I've just got some stuff
好的, 我有些事
I got to take care of, okay?
要处理一下, 好吗?
Okay.
好的
Mrs. van de Kamp.
VAN DE KAMP夫人
Hello, John.
你好, JOHN
I'm sorry to drop by on you unannounced.
抱歉我不请自来了
Do you have a moment?
你有时间吗?
Sure.
当然
So...
那么...
What can I do for you?
有什么我能为你效劳的?
Well, I'll tell you.
我来告诉你
My daughter is planning on giving you her virginity,
我女儿准备把她的第一次给你
And I would consider it a personal favor
我希望你帮我一个忙
If you wouldn't take it.
不要接受她
Hey.
- 嗨
hey.
嗨
So what's the word on Tim?
TIM的情况怎么样了?
He came through the triple bypass
他身上插着三根导管
With flying colors.
不过已经没事了
Ah, thank god.
谢天谢地
Of course, it's not all coming up roses.
当然, 也不全是好消息
He's not going to be able to come back to work for...
他将有4到4个半月...
4, 4 1/2 months.
不能参加工作
Oh.
哦
What?
什么?
The company still needs to expand, so I figure,
公司依然需要扩张, 所以我想
They need a fit, heart-smart guy like me
他们需要有人替代 一个像我这样的聪明人
To step up, take the ball.
挺身而出, 接过重担
You're going after Tim Duggan's promotion?
你要去争取TIM DUGGAN的晋升机会?
No. I already got it.
不. 我已经得到了
You should have seen me.
你应该看到我今天所做的事
I walked straight into Peterson's office,
我径直冲进PETERSON的办公室
and I told him
告诉他
that he would be a fool to hold Duggan's promotion.
如果他升DUGGAN的职, 他将是个傻子
You called your boss a fool?
你叫你老板傻子?
I did.
是的
That was risky in retrospect,
回想起来那真是冒险啊
but you know what? still, he gave me the job.
但你知道么, 他依然给我了那份工作
Oh, my god! That's great.
哦, 上帝啊! 太好了
Honey, it's me.
亲爱的, 这就是我
I'm the man, I've got the whole west coast
我是那个成功者 我得到了整个西海岸
-
Oh, my
哦, 我的
- what?
- 什么?
What? the whole west coast?
什么? 整个西海岸?
I thought you were going after an in-house position.
我以为你追求的是一个在总部的职位
No, no, no. I'm setting up new offices from Seattle to L.A.
不, 不, 不. 我将从西雅图开始 设立办公室一直到洛杉矶
I-I told you that.
我-我告诉过你
No.
没有
No, you didn't.
你没有
Okay.
好吧
Well, so it's going to be a little bit more travel, but
所以将会有一些些更多的旅行, 但
-
More travel?
更多的旅行?
Tom, you're barely here half the time as it is,
TOM, 你现在只有一半时间在家里
And now you're going to have, what, twice the workload?
而现在你的工作量又要翻倍?
Honey, please, don't ruin this.
亲爱的, 拜托, 不要破坏这一切
I'm sorry, but you should have consulted with me.
对不起, 但是你应该和我谈谈
I did. you told me to stop being a shrinking violet
我谈了啊 你告诉我不要做一个羞怯的人
and to step up.
要挺身而出
I thought this was an in-house position.
我以为这是一个在总部的职位
Okay, I'm going to go shower.
好吧, 我要去冲澡了
Look, wait, wait.
等一下, 等一下
I know what this means to you.
我知道这对你意味着什么
No, you don't.
不, 你不知道
No, you don't. I am 41 years old.
不, 你不知道, 我41岁了
If I don't make vice president now,
如果我现在不能做到副主管
It's never going to happen.
永远都做不到了
This is my career. it's
这是我的职业, 这
- it's important to me.
- 这对我很重要
So was mine, but I'm here, aren't I?
我的也是, 但我在这儿, 不是吗?
I'm going to take the job.
我要接受这个工作
She said that you broke up with her
她说你和她分手
because she refused to have sex.
因为她拒绝和你做爱
Wow. um...
喔. 嗯...
Okay, here's the deal
好吧, 事实是这样的
-
I said that, but it was just an excuse.
我是那么说了, 但那只是个借口
I mean, the truth is...
我是说, 事实是...
I wasn't that into her.
我并不那么喜欢她
Really?
真的?
And she was always so proud of never having done it,
她总是那么骄傲于从未做过那个
I figured, hey, this is my way out.
所以我想, 嗨, 那是我的出路
Well, she feels very passionately about you.
但她很喜欢你
Well, don't get me wrong. she's nice.
请别误会, 她是个好女孩
The truth is...
事实是...
There's someone else.
我有别人了
Oh.
哦
Are you going steady?
你们的关系稳定了吗?
Not exactly.
并没有
We were seeing each other pretty regularly,
我们以前经常见面
but this other lady
但这另一位女士
- girl
- 女孩
-
She sort of dumped me.
她甩了我
Oh, I see.
哦, 我明白了
Well, look, I'll talk to Danielle,
我会和DANIELLE谈谈
And don't worry
不用担心
-
I'll let her down gently.
我会很温柔地拒绝他的
Um, actually, I would prefer if you didn't.
嗯, 事实上, 我希望你不要温柔
Huh?
哈?
I know my daughter. she's very determined,
我了解我的女儿, 她是个坚定不移的人
and unless you're really firm with her,
除非你和她明确地说清楚
She's going to continue to think that there's hope.
不然她会一直以为还有希望
Okay. I'll be firm.
好的, 我会明确地说清楚的
Better still...
最好...
be brutal.
残忍一点
Decided to indulge your sweet tooth, huh?
决定纵容一下你的牙齿, 哈?
I'll be dead inside a year.
不出一年我就要死了
I got bigger things to worry about
我有比腰围更重要的事
Than my waistline.
要担心
So...
那么...
Who's the woman they think you killed?
他们以为你杀了哪个女人?
Martha Huber, local busybody.
MARTHA HUBER 当地一个好管闲事的人
I thought her murder was random.
我以为她只是偶然被杀
Nothing random about her jewelry ending up in your garage.
但她的珠宝出现在你的车库里 可是一点都不偶然啊
Did you kill her?
是你杀了她吗?
No.
不
Whoever set me up did a good job, though.
不过不管是谁陷害了我 他做得很不错
The cops are all over me.
警察都来查我了
You're getting close to something.
你已经接近一些事情了
Well, if I am close, I don't see it.
就算真的如此, 我也没觉得
What I'm saying is people leave trails.
我的意思是人们都会留下痕迹
One of those trails will lead to Deirdre.
而那些痕迹中的一个就会指向DIERDRE
Whoever set you up must know that.
陷害你的人肯定知道这一点
Yeah. well, maybe.
是啊, 也许吧
But I won't be much good to you locked up.
但如果我被关进去了, 就没什么意义了
I'm rich, Mike.
我有钱, MIKE
One of the best things about being rich
有钱的好处之一
is the security of knowing
就是一种安全感
you can buy your way out of any problem.
知道你可以用钱解决一切问题
I'm not taking my money to the grave.
我不想把钱带到棺材里
I'm going to use it to save your ass.
我会用它来保护你
Mrs. Sol韘.
SOLIS夫人
Hello, Justin.
你好, JUSTIN
Hey. What are you doing here?
嗨. 你来这儿干什么呢?
I am here to talk to your roommate.
我来和你的室友谈谈
John?
JOHN?
I-I didn't think you guys talked anymore.
我-我以为你们不再交谈了
Well, now we have something to talk about
现在我们有些事情要谈谈了
-
You.
关于你
Me.
我
Yes. I'm going to tell him how you're trying
是的. 我要告诉他你试图
to blackmail me into sleeping with you.
要挟我和你上床
I wonder how he'll react.
不知道他会有什么反应
Mrs. Sol韘
SOLIS夫人
-
You can't talk to John about that.
你不能和JOHN说那事
Oh, I can,
哦, 我能
And I will, you little worthless piece of crap.
而且我会的, 你这没用的垃圾
Listen, Mrs. Sol韘, I'm sorry.
听我说, SOLIS夫人, 我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I didn't want to blackmail you.
对不起, 我并不想要挟你
Then why did you?
那你为什么那么做?
I really needed to sleep with you.
我真的很需要和你上床
Why?
为什么?
Because...
因为...
I think I might be gay.
我可能是同性恋
Oh.
哦
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
爸爸! 爸爸! 爸爸!
Hey!
嗨!
Dad! Daddy!
爸爸! 爸爸!
Dad!
爸爸!
How you doing, guys? What's up?
你们怎么样, 伙计们? 怎么啦?
Oh, we went out for burgers,
哦, 我们出去吃汉堡了
and the boys knew you wouldn't be home
孩子们知道
till after, um, bedtime,
你不会在就寝时间前回来
and so we decided to pop in and visit the new V.P.
所以我们决定给新上任的副主管 一个“突然袭击”
Yeah, well, check it out.
你们看
I finally got an office with a window.
我终于有一个带窗户的办公室了
Yeah, it's all about the window.
是啊, 一切都是为了窗户啊
Hey, guys.
嗨, 伙计们
Hey, who wants chair rides?
嗨, 谁想坐转转椅?
Me! Me! Me!
我! ! 我!
Come on, out this way. here we go.
来, 这边来. 来吧
Here we go, guys. Ready?
来吧, 伙计们. 准备好了吗?
Yeah, daddy!
爸爸, 好棒啊!
Now hold on! Try to hold on!
抓稳了! 努力抓稳了!
Checking out the new executive digs?
来看新的行政主管?
Oh.
哦
You know it.
你明白的
Can I tell you a little secret?
我能告诉你一个小秘密吗?
Sure.
当然
Dan wanted to hold the promotion over for Tim Duggan.
DAN想要把晋升的机会留给TIM DUGGAN
And I'm the one that convinced him
而我说服了他
to give it to tom.
把机会给TOM
Really?
真的?
Uh-huh.
嗯哼
Tom is such a workhorse,
TOM是一个不折不扣的工作狂
and he wanted it so badly.
他非常想得到这次机会
Yeah, he certainly did.
是啊, 他的确是
What is wrong? aren't you happy about this promotion?
怎么了? 你不为这次升职开心吗?
Lynette realized it was in her best interest
(LYNETTE意识到)
to lie to the boss's wife...
(她最好对老板的妻子撒个谎...)
Well, it's great, obviously.
非常开心, 当然了
Thank you.
谢谢
Provided she wasn't too convincing.
(倘若她的话不是那么令人信服)
Of course,
当然
I mean, I will miss him,
我是说, 我会想他的
being gone all the time.
一直奔波在外
He'll be bringing in more money,
他能赚回更多的钱
But he is going to miss the birthdays,
但他也将错过生日庆祝
baseball games,
棒球比赛
first steps...
婴儿迈出的头几步...
But that's the trade-off.
有得必有失
Right?
对吧?
I just hope one day,
我只是希望某一天
Tom doesn't look back and regret being gone so much.
TOM不会回顾过去并后悔离家太久
Well, I better get out there before they break something.
嗯, 我最好赶在他们打破什么之前过去
Of course. I will see you soon.
好的, 以后见
So have you been acting on these feelings?
你是不是装出这些感觉的?
I got a buddy. we get together,
我有个好兄弟, 我们经常在一起
We mess around.
消磨时光
But it's no big deal.
但没什么特别的
It's just lately, I've been starting to, like,
只是最近, 我慢慢开始
Care about him, and I don't know how to handle it.
对他有感觉, 我也不知道该怎么办
Wow.
喔
Yeah, and I thought if I sleep with somebody like you,
是啊, 于是我想 如果我和你这样的人上床了
I'll know for sure,
我就能确定了
and I can stop freaking out about this.
也不必再为这事烦恼
Yeah, but why me? You're a good-looking kid.
但为什么是我呢? 你是个英俊的男孩
Why don't you test-drive someone your own age?
为什么不在你的同龄人里“试试车”呢?
Girls talk.
女孩子们闲话太多
If I start something with somebody
如果我和某一个做那个
and it doesn't...
而结果...
work out,
我不能
everybody at school will find out.
那么学校里的每一个人都知道了
And I figured I could trust you,
我想我能信任你
'cause you have a husband and all.
因为你有丈夫
Well, I guess that makes sense, in a...
我想你说的也有点道理, 从...
Weird sort of way.
一个古怪的角度来看
You know, my buddy and I, we've been messing around
我的好兄弟和我, 我们在一起
for quite a while, and...
已经有一段时间了, 而...
this whole time, I just kept telling myself
这整个过程中我一直告诉自己
that it didn't really mean anything, you know?
那并不意味着任何事 你明白我的意思吗?
I guess I've just been kidding myself, huh?
我想我一直在欺骗自己
We're all in denial about something.
我们都会拒绝承认一些事
But you're finally facing the truth,
但你最终能够面对现实
and I think that's sort of brave.
我觉得那很勇敢
Thanks.
谢谢
I should probably go.
我该走了
Uh, just so you know,
嗯, 只是想让你知道
I never would have told Mr. Sol韘 about you and John.
我从未告诉SOLIS先生你和JOHN的事
I may be gay, but I'm not a jerk.
我也许是个同性恋, 但我不是一个混蛋
Did you feel anything?
你有什么感觉吗?
Not really.
似乎没有
You're definitely gay.
你肯定是个同性恋
Hi.
嗨
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you at night, ms. Mayer,
嗨. 抱歉在晚上打扰你, MAYER小姐
but I was hoping that maybe you could
但我希望你能够
come down to the station with me,
和我一起到警局去一下
just answer a few more questions.
只是再回答几个问题
Now? Well, I-I'm sorry.
现在? 对-对不起
My
我的
- my daughter and I were going to go see a movie tonight.
- 我的女儿和我 今晚要去看场电影
Mom...
妈妈...
We can do it another night. I'll be fine.
我们可以另找一天再去. 我没问题
Uh...
嗯...
Let me get my purse.
- 让我去拿一下我的包
Great.
好的
Are you sure?
你确定不用今天去?
Yeah.
是的
Well, I'm sure I won't be late.
我不会太晚回来的
Okay. bye.
好的, 拜拜
Bye.
拜拜
You said that Mike came to your house
你说MIKE7号那晚大约在10点
around 10:00 pm on the night of the 7th.
来到你家
Um...
嗯...
Am I supposed to talk into the camera or...
我应该对着摄像机说还是...
No, no. just
不, 不. 只要
- just talk to me.
- 只要对着我说
Okay. uh, yes.
好的. 嗯, 好
He came over around 10:00.
他大约10点过来的
Do you know of any tension between Mike and Martha Huber?
你是否知道MIKE和MARTHA HUBER 有什么不和?
No.
不知道
Were you aware that Mike was shot recently?
你是否知道MIKE最近被射伤了?
Yes.
是的
On Valentine's day.
在情人节那天
And do you know how that came about?
你知道他为什么被射伤吗?
He dropped his gun cleaning it.
他擦枪的时候枪掉了
Ms. Mayer, with all due respect,
MAYER小姐, 恕我冒昧
I've been working around guns for yes.
我用枪已经用了很多年了
I've never seen one discharge when it hits the ground.
我从没看到过枪落地后会开火的
Someone has to pull the trigger.
肯定有人按动了扳机
Well, I wouldn't know about that.
我可不知道
Were you aware there was a home invasion
你是否知道有一起侵入他宅案
three blocks from you on Pine Avenue
发生于PINE街离你家3个路口之处
day before Valentine's?
- 在情人节的前一天?
No.
不知道
The intruder was shot in the stomach.
子弹射到了侵入者的胃部
Where was Mike's wound?
MIKE的伤口在哪里?
The stomach.
胃部
Do you love him?
你是否爱他?
What?
什么?
What does that have to do with
那有什么关系
-
It's just that sometimes people do stupid things
只是有时候人们会做一些傻事
when they're in love.
当他们陷入爱河的时候
I should know. I've been married four times.
我应当知道. 我已经结了四次婚了
Tell me the truth.
告诉我事实
he wasn't with you that night, was he?
他那晚没有和你在一起, 不是吗?
He asked you to lie for him, Didn't he?
他要你为他撒谎, 不是吗?
No, he didn't. He was with me,
不, 他是和我在一起
and Mike wouldn't kill anybody. I'm sure of that.
还有, MIKE没有杀任何人, 我很肯定
Mike Delfino
MIKE DELFINO
-
convicted 1987,
于1987年被定罪
did 5 1/2 years for drug trafficking
服刑5年半, 罪名是偷运毒品
and manslaughter.
和过失杀人
You want a coffee? I'm going to go for coffee.
你想来杯咖啡吗? 我要去倒一杯
So is she covering for her guy?
她是在为她的男友掩盖真相吗?
Nah, she's just a sucker.
不, 她只是个笨蛋
I guess no one's in the pool yet.
我想泳池里还没有人
Are you going to swim?
你想去游泳吗?
Please. I just spent, like, an hour blowing out my hair.
拜托. 我刚刚花了大概一小时吹了头发
Good luck, man.
祝你好运, 伙计
I'll
我们
- I'll see you later, okay?
- 我们晚点见, 好吗?
Okay.
好
Hey.
嗨
Uh, hey, I've got a surprise for you.
哈, 嗨, 我给你准备了一份惊喜
Want to go somewhere and talk?
想找个地方谈谈吗?
Yeah. We should talk.
是的, 我们应该谈谈
Hi. You made it.
嗨. 你成功了
Andrew's here. I didn't think he'd come.
ANDREW也来了. 我以为他不会来的
Yeah, he brought a lot of friends.
是啊, 他带来了一堆朋友
They're acting like total jerks.
他们就象是一群傻子
Alert the media.
要惊动媒体了
But I don't care. You're here now.
但我不介意, 因为你来了
This is going to be great.
我们会很开心的
Come on, man. Let's go.
来吧, 伙计. 我们走
Danielle.
DANIELLE
Don't touch me!
别碰我!
hope you can swim.
希望你会游泳
Can you possibly take it easy?
你能不能悠着点儿啊?
It's cool, man. Look
这很酷, 伙计. 看
- it floats.
- 它能漂呢
All right? Relax. It's a party.
没事吧? 放轻松. 这是个派对
You're the main party animal, right?
你是派对的主角, 不是吗?
Am I right?
不是吗?
I guess.
我想是的
All right. Well, then act like it.
很好, 那就表现出来啊
Come on. Give me a howl.
来啊. 嚎两声听听
Come on, you're the host. Revel in it.
来吧, 你是主人. 应该投入一点
Give me a howl.
嚎两声听听
There you go.
算了吧
You okay?
你没事吧?
What do I care?
我干嘛要介意啊?
He's nothing.
他无足轻重
I could take care of him if I wanted to.
如果我想解决掉他, 我就能做到
What do you mean?
什么意思?
I know where my Mom kept her gun.
我知道我妈妈把枪放在哪里
That's not funny, Zach.
那并不有趣, ZACH
Well, if you think about it, yeah, it kind of is.
如果你仔细想想的话 那也许是有趣的
Julie.
JULIE
Hey, Danielle.
嗨, DANIELLE
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
I just want to go home.
我只想回家
Can we go?
我们能走了吗?
Sure.
当然
Julie.
JULIE
I'm taking Danielle home.
我送DANIELLE回家
Are you coming back?
你还回来吗?
I don't think so.
不回来了
Oh.
哦
So how was the PTA meeting?
家长会怎么样?
Long. Ha ha.
冗长, 哈哈
So Peterson called me into his office today.
PETERSON今天把我叫到他的办公室
Really?
真的?
Yeah, he, uh...
是啊, 他, 嗯...
He changed his mind. he's going to...
他改变了主意, 打算...
hold that promotion for Duggan.
把那个晋升的机会留给DUGGAN
Oh.
哦
Yeah, it's
那
- it's
- 那
- it's fine.
- 那没关系
You know, I'm glad, really.
我很开心, 真的
I didn't want to work all those long hours,
我不想工作那么长时间
and you know how I hate flying.
你也知道我对于飞行的厌恶
It just does, you know, horrible things to my back,
它让我的背部觉得很不舒服
and, god, with all that extra stress,
还有, 上帝, 那额外的压力
I would have ended up exactly like Tim Duggan
10年之后, 我会落得
10 years from now, so...
像TIM DUGGAN那样, 所以...
Yeah, of course.
是啊, 当然
So it's
所以
- it's over.
- 事情结束了
Look, you're going to make vice president
你将来会成为副主管的
One of these days.
不远的将来
You know what? it's okay, honest.
你知道么, 这真的没关系, 老实说
I am, uh...
我, 嗯...
I'm really glad that it worked out this way.
我真的很高兴这件事能以这种方式结束
Oh, god, you scared me.
哦, 上帝啊, 你吓到我了
How'd it go?
事情进行得怎么样?
Went just peachy.
“好”极了
And humiliating and shocking.
我又羞又惊
Susan
SUSAN
-
How could you?
怎么会呢?
God
天啊
- "Susan, do you trust me?"
- “SUSAN, 你信任我吗?”
"Yes, of course I do." Oh, I'm such an idiot.
“是的, 我当然信任你” 哦, 我真是个笨蛋
And you're such a liar.
你真是个大骗子
Oh, and apparently, a killer and a drug dealer.
哦, 看上去, 还是一个杀手和毒贩子
That's just quite a personal ad you've got going there.
你在那儿可有一个 相当不错的“个人广告”啊
Susan, I came to Wisteria Lane
SUSAN, 我来到WISTERIA LANE
-
Stop! Stop, Mike! Just stop.
住嘴! 住嘴, MIKE! 不要说了
If you keep talking,
如果你继续说下去
you're going to work your way into my heart,
你就能占据我的心
And I just don't want you
而我就是不想
Anywhere near my heart...
再让你接近我的心...
Ever.
永远也不
Julie?
JULIE?
Mommy needs a hug.
妈妈需要一个拥抱
Julie?
JULIE?
Is Julie in there? Julie Mayer?
JULIE在吗? JULIE MAYER?
I don't know. It's pretty dead in there.
我不知道. 里面基本上没人了
Julie Alexandra Mayer!
JULIE ALEXANDRA MAYER!
Oh, Julie, Zach, this is ridiculous!
哦, JULIE, ZACH, 这真是太荒唐了!
You can't hold your breath forever!
你不可能永远屏住呼吸!
Oh!
哦!
Oh, you might as well just stay under there
哦, 你最好一直呆在下面
and never come up for air, 'cause when you do,
永远不要上来换气 如果你胆敢伸出头来
I'm going to choke the living daylights out of you!
我就掐得你昏天又暗地!
Is my daughter under there?
我的女儿在下面吗?
I'm not
我不是
- I'm not gay.
- 我不是同性恋
I
我
- okay.
- 好的
I'm
我
- I'm sorry.
- 我很抱歉
I'll just
我
-
I'm just going to leave those right there.
我就把那个留在这儿了
Oh! I'm fine.
哦! 我没事
It's good. you just
很好.
- you know
你们
-
--
Did
你们
- did you see
- 你们看到
- no. Goodbye.
- 不. 拜拜
Sell the house. Are you crazy?
把房子卖了. 你疯了吗?
Carlos, we can't afford to live here anymore.
CARLOS, 我们住不起这房子了
But if our lawyer gets the justice department
但如果我们的律师能让司法部
To unfreeze the bank accounts, then
解冻我的账户, 那么
-
Then what? Huh? Finish the sentence, Carlos.
那么怎样? 哈? 把话说完啊, CARLOS
We have tons of legal bills, you've lost all your clients,
我们有一大堆的法定账单 而你又失去了所有的客户
And even with our savings, we're screwed.
就算是加上我们的积蓄, 我们也完了
But
但是
-
It's our house.
这是我们的房子
Honey, I know.
亲爱的, 我知道
I love this place, too.
我也爱着这个地方
I just
只是
- I think it's time for us to face the music.
- 我想我们还是面对现实比较好
I never thought I'd be poor at this stage of my life.
我从没想到在这个年纪我会如此贫穷
You know, Carlos,
CARLOS, 你知道
I've been broke a lot of times in my life,
我一生中破产过很多次
But I've never been poor,
但我从没有贫穷过
Because poor is just a state of mind.
因为贫穷只是脑子里的一种观念
And right now,
而现在
You and I are just...
你和我只是...
Without funds?
缺少资金?
Exactly.
完全正确
I guess we could get an apartment,
我想我们可以找套公寓
Start over.
重新开始
Who knows?
谁知道呢?
It might even be fun.
甚至也可能会很有趣
And once we're back on our feet...
一旦我们东山再起了...
We'll get a house as big as this one.
我们就买一幢和这一样大的房子
Bigger.
更大的
So I get my wife this dog for her birthday.
我送给我妻子一条狗作为生日礼物
A stray from the pound.
动物收容所里的一只流浪狗
Cheapest gift I've ever gotten her,
这是我送她的礼物里最便宜的一个
And she loves it, so I'm a genius, right?
但她喜欢它, 我是个天才, 对吧?
Then I find out it's got this weird blood disease.
后来我发觉它有一种古怪的血液病
Now I'm laying out $600 a month for doggie medicine
现在我每个月要花600美元在狗药上
for this mutt, and I'm a genius, right?
为了就这只杂种狗 我是个天才, 对吧?
Aw, don't be cynical. you did something nice,
哦, 不要挖苦自己了 你做了一些不错的事
made your wife happy.
让你的妻子很开心
Now...
现在...
let's talk about what's going to make you happy.
让我们谈谈谁来让你开心一下
Yes, each new day in suburbia
(是的, 在郊区, 新的一天的到来)
brings with it a new set of lies.
(总是伴随着一系列的谎言)
The worst are the ones we tell ourselves
(而其中最糟的是那些我们用来 自己骗自己的)
before we fall asleep.
(在我们入睡之前)
We whisper them in the dark,
(我们在黑暗中低声地)
telling ourselves...
(告诉自己...)
we're happy.
(我们很快乐)
or...
(或者...)
that he's happy.
(他很快乐)
that we can change.
(我们可以改变)
Or that he will change his mind.
(或者他会改变主意)
We persuade ourselves we can live with our sins...
(我们说服自己带着罪恶继续生活...)
or that we can live without him.
(或者我们没有他也一样可以生活)
Yes, each night before we fall asleep,
(是的, 每天晚上在我们入睡前)
we lie to ourselves
(我们对自己说谎)
in the desperate, desperate hope
(近乎绝望地希望着)
that come morning, it will all be true.
(当黎明到来的时候, 一切都能成真)